hioxindia.com 2008-05-11

# Contact Address for HIOX INDIA - Coimbatore, Tamilnadu

**HIOX INDIA Privacy Policy**

By accessing or using the hioxindia.com (HIOX INDIA) web site, you agree to the terms of the hioxindia.com (HIOX INDIA) Privacy Policy, as outlined below. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site. HIOX INDIA reserves the right to change its Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion. Your use of this site will be subject to the most current version of the Privacy Policy at the time of such use. 

Collection of personal information  
When you engage in certain activities on this site, such as ordering products, downloading software, or entering contests, hioxindia.com (HIOX INDIA) may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however, HIOX INDIA may ask that you provide us personal information, such as your first and last name, mailing address (including zip code), e-mail address, telephone and other numbers, and other personal identifying information. When ordering products or services on the site, you may be asked to provide a credit card number. Depending upon the activity, some of the information that we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity. 

In the process of administering our site, we maintain and track usage through Web server logs. Web server logs provide such information as what types of browsers are accessing our site, what pages receive high traffic, and the times of day our servers experience significant load. We use this information to improve the content and navigation features of our site. It is not used to personally identify you. 

How your personal information is used  
hioxindia.com (HIOX INDIA) collects your information in order to record and support your participation in the activities you select. The information that you provide is also used as part of our effort to keep you informed about special offers and other products and services of HIOX INDIA and selected third parties. 

How we share your personal information  
We will not sell, rent or lease to others telephone numbers or e-mail addresses. We will share the personal data you provide only with other hioxindia.com (HIOX INDIA) entities and/or business partners who are acting on our behalf for the uses described above, except as provided below (see Consent). 

Consent  
HIOX INDIA will use and share the personally identifiable information you provided to us in ways related to those described above. We reserve the right to disclose any and all pertinent customer information to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate. 

Contacting Us:  
If you have any questions about our site, this privacy policy, or our general procedures, please Contact Us at support@hioxindia.com.   

* * *

Hosting customers from India, Canada, USA, Srilanka, Singapore, United Kingdom, Malaysia...   
Serving Indian customer from coimbatore, chennai, hyderabad, kerela, mumbai, bangalore, delhi, kolkata, pune, ahmedabad, .....
